Guide to the Duke Ellington School of the Arts collection, 1966-2014 MS2329
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audio and visual materials, 1966-2003; Series 6
  - Slides, 1966-1996; Series 6 Subseries 4
    - Leslie Delaine, B-, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Linda Jones 200/, 3 October 1986; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Linda Jones Ass. #1, B- 1-2:30, Photojournalism, Media/Literary, Arts Dept., Duke Ellington School of Arts, 17 September 1986; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Linda Jones - David and Carolyn's Class, 29 October 1986; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Lisa Yearwood, B, 1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Lit. Arts, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Lit. Arts NYC Trip Columbia University, 1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Literary Arts Portraits/Rejects, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Literary Arts with Computers - Rejects, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Looking for Heroes, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Looking for Heroes/Rejects, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Lynn Whitfield, March 1975; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Margaret and Penn Center Show Scenes, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Maurice Veal Rejects, 1982; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Michelle at 1845, 1978; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Motojicho, 1970-1978; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Motojicho/Blk V. Art, March 1970; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Multi-Cultural Day, 1993-1994; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Natasha Alston, 1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Natasha Alston Assignment #1, 2 October 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Natasha Alston - Critique, November 1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Portraits of Gloria Keys, Marshall Oct. 3 7150, B-, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Rejects, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Rejects, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Rejects, 1987, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Rhonda Sr. Slides, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Rickie Williams, 1991; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Rikki Lights, March 1978; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Robert Howard, 20 April 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Senior Rejects, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Shercrisha Finly, March 1992; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Slides, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Slides, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Slides, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Slides, 1976-1991; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Slides (1/2), 1978-1995; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Slides (2/2), 1978-1995; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Slides, May 1979; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Slides, October 1979; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Slides, 1979-1984; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Slides, March 1980; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Slides, October 1986; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Slides, 1986, 1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Slides, 1986-1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Slides, 1986-1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Slides, 1986-1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Slides, 1986-1991; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Slides, 1987-1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Slides, 1987-1994; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Slides, 1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Slides, 1990-1995; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Slides, December 1992; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Slides, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Slides [Alex Perriera], 1993; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Slides [Charlotte Hayes], 1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Slides [Holly Zepp], n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Slides [L. Mosley/Intro/Shateria], October 1991; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley] #1, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley] #2, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley] #4, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley] (1/4), 1975-1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley] (2/4), 1974-1994; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley] (3/4), 1976-1996; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley] (4/4), 1976-1996; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley/Aaron-Jeria], November 1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley/Christine-Rashida], November 1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosely/Cynthia-Sherenska], November 1991; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley (Glannio)], January 1992; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Slides [Leigh H. Mosley/Holly?], May 1991; Serie 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley/Jeria], B-, November 1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Slides [Leigh H. Mosley/Lajuanda], 1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley/Rashida], B-, November 1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosley/Seniors/Darl], May 1991; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Slides [Leigh Mosely/Tina], 1991; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Slides [Lew Berry], 1992; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Slides [Mosley-Alston], May 1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Slides [Mosley/Angela], June 1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Slides [Mosley and Kaleda], June 1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Slides [Mosley/Kim Bowling], June 1989; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Slides [Mosley/Kim Bowling-Tiffany], June 1989; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Slides [Mosley/Marlena], June 1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Slides [Mosley/Montique], June 1989; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Slides [Niquette Jean], 1989-1991; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Slides [N. Johnson], October 1975; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Smoking Session at Bill's, March 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Stills, B.B. Streets, Chamberlain, February 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Sundiata and Gloria (Assign 1), 17 April 1986; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Tamiko Kirk, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - The Farm, 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Theatre Department at Malcolm X Park, June 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Theresa (Flag Woman) Michelle, May 1979; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Time Odyssey Crowd/Cover, 30 April 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Tina Dederschelk, February 1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Tina Dederscheck Seniors Ass. #1, October 1989; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Tina Dederscheck #2, 1989; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Tore Carmina, April 1993; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Tracey Hawkins Ass. #1, B- 1-2:30, September-December 1986; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Vocal Music/Music Instrument, 1987-1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Yvette, Deneen, Joe Williams with Donald Ceace and Carolynn Jones - Rejects, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 18)